Contact

hatterk@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kimberly-hatter-aa994b42 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Medical/Surgical ICU Critical Care

Certifications

Basic Life Support
Advanced Cardiac Life Support
Board Certified Adult Gerontology
Nurse Practitioner

Kimberly Hatter

Adult Gerontology Nurse Practitioner (MSN, AGPCNP-BC) Houston, Texas

Summary

Experienced Nurse Practitioner with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Medical-Surgical, Intensive Care, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), and Healthcare Information Technology (HIT). Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Science in Nursing focused in Adult Gerontology Primary Care Nurse Practitioner from The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston.

Experience

Houston Methodist-TMH Physician Organization Nurse Practitioner May 2015 - Present (5 years 1 month) Liver Transplant Surgery

CHI St. Luke's Health - Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center RN, BSN, CCRN

June 2006 - May 2015 (9 years)

CVRR/Cooley 8 A&B ICU(Organ Transplant, LVADs, IABP, CRRT)

Christus Spohn Health System RN, BSN January 2002 - May 2006 (4 years 5 months) Spohn-Shoreline (Telemetry Unit)

Telemetry/Step-down Unit

West Florida Hospital RN June 1999 - January 2002 (2 years 8 months) Surgical Progressive Care Unit

Progressive Care Unit

Education

The University of Texas Medical Branch

Master of Science in Nursing, Adult Gerontology Primary Care Nurse

Practitioner · (2013 - 2014)

University of South Alabama
Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (1999 - 2001)

Pensacola Junior College Associate of Science (A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1997 - 1999)

Concorde Career Institute-Jacksonville Medical Assisting, Medical/Clinical Assistant · (1992 - 1993)